<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
   Copyright © 2021. Richard P. Parkins, M. A.
   Released under GPL V3 or later
  -->

<resources xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools">
    <string name="widget">widget</string>
    <string name="clock">clock</string>
    <string name="app_name">SecondsClock</string>
    <string name="app_label">Seconds Clock</string>
    <string name="nosysclock">Cannot find system clock app.</string>
    <string name="noclockpermission">Cannot launch system clock:
        try giving SecondsClock permission SET_ALARMS.</string>
    <string name="gosysclock">Go to system clock app</string>
    <string name="helpsysclock">Touch this button to go to the device\'s
        default clock app.</string>
    <string name="confignewwidget">Configure new widget</string>
    <string name="helpnewwidget">Touch this button to set the configuration
        for new widgets. To create a new widget, long press in an empty
        space in your home screen.</string>
    <string name="configoldwwidget">Configure existing widget</string>
    <string name="helpoldwidget">Touch this button to configure a widget that
        you have created previously: you will be sent back to your home screen
        and the first widget (from this app) that you touch will take you
        to the widget configure screen for that widget.</string>
    <string name="actionoldwidget">When you see your home screen, if necessary
        move to the appropriate page, and touch the widget that you want
        to configure.</string>
    <string name="confignightclock">Configure full screen clock</string>
    <string name="helpnightclock">Touch this button to configure the
        full screen clock.</string>
    <string name="runnightclock">Run full screen clock</string>
    <string name="helprunclock">Touch this button to run
        the full screen clock.</string>
    <string name="appwidget_text">Clock</string>
    <string name="app_widget_description">1x1 seconds clock</string>
    <string name="demohelp">This shows what the widget looks like.
        If there is currently no home screen widget, the size may not be correct
        because SecondsClock can\'t find out what size the widget would be:
        it will use an estimate for the size of a 1x1 widget.
        If you resize the widget on the home screen to a larger size,
        the widget will rearrange its layout to use a larger font size.
        The background pattern shows the effect of the widget background
        in case it is not transparent.</string>
    <string name="longpresslabel">Long press here for help information.</string>
    <string name="mainactivityhelp">This screen allows you to choose what to do next.
        Long press on any of the buttons for a longer description of what it does.
        This could have been a menu, but that would make you do an unnecessary
        extra click.</string>
    <string name="widgetconfighelp">This screen allows you to configure a widget.
        If you came here from a particular widget, it reconfigures that: if you came here
        from the top level screen, it sets the the configuration for new widgets.
        You can make multiple widgets with different configurations.
        Long press on anything for a longer description of what it does.</string>
    <string name="clockconfighelp">This screen allows you to configure the full screen clock.
        Long press on anything for a longer description of what it does.</string>
    <string name="show_time">Show time in widget</string>
    <string name="showtimehelp">If this box is checked, the widget will
        display the time in locale-appropriate format.</string>
    <string name="show_seconds">Show time with seconds in widget</string>
    <string name="showsecondshelp">If this box is checked, the widget will
        display the time in locale-appropriate format including seconds.
        This will increase battery drain since the widget has to update itself
        every second.</string>
    <string name="show_short_weekday">Show abbreviated day name
        in %1s.</string>
    <string name="showshortweekdayhelp">If this box is checked, the %1s will
        display the locale-appropriate abbreviation for the day of the
        week.</string>
    <string name="show_long_weekday">Show full day name in %1s.</string>
    <string name="showlongweekdayhelp">If this box is checked, the %1s will
        display the locale-appropriate full name for the day of the
        week.</string>
    <string name="show_short_date">Show numeric date in %1s.</string>
    <string name="showshortdatehelp">If this box is checked, the %1s will
        display the locale-appropriate numeric date. If the numeric date
        is shown, the full date cannot be shown as well.</string>
    <string name="show_month_day">Show day of month in %1s.</string>
    <string name="showmonthdayhelp">If this box is checked, the %1s will
        display the day of the month.</string>
    <string name="show_short_month">Show abbreviated month name in %1s.</string>
    <string name="showshortmonthhelp">If this box is checked, the %1s will
        display the locale-appropriate abbreviation for the month.</string>
    <string name="show_long_month">Show full month name in %1s.</string>
    <string name="showlongmonthhelp">If this box is checked, the %1s will
        display the locale-appropriate full name for the month.</string>
    <string name="show_year">Show year in %1s.</string>
    <string name="showyearhelp">If this box is checked, the %1s will
        display the (Gregorian) year.</string>
    <string name="set_bg_colour">Set widget background colour</string>
    <string name="setbgcolourhelp">Touch this button to show a colour
        chooser screen for the background colour of the widget.</string>
    <string name="set_fg_colour">Set widget text colour</string>
    <string name="setfgcolourhelp">Touch this button to show a colour
        chooser screen for the text colour of the widget.</string>
    <string name="fghelp">Touch anywhere in this pane to select
        the saturation and value of the text colour of the widget.</string>
    <string name="bghelp">Touch anywhere in this pane to select
        the saturation and value of the background colour of the widget.</string>
    <string name="backgroundcolourhelp">This screen provides sliders
        to set the hue, red, green, blue, and opacity
        of the clock widget\'s background. You can also type in values
        for red, green, blue, and opacity or pick a colour from the
        map of saturation and value for a hue.</string>
    <string name="textcolourhelphelp">This screen provides sliders
        to set the hue, red, gree, and blue components of the colour
        of the clock widget\'s text. You can also type in values
        for red, green, and blue, or pick a colour from the
        map of saturation and value for a hue.</string>
    <string name="setredsliderhelp">Move the thumb on this slider
        to adjust the amount of red in the colour.</string>
    <string name="redvaluehelp">This number shows the actual amount of red
        in the colour on a scale from 0 to 255. You can edit the number.
        A single tap on the number will put the edit cursor where you tap;
        a double tap on the number will select the whole of it;
        a long tap on the number will display this message.</string>
    <string name="setgreensliderhelp">Move the thumb on this slider
        to adjust the amount of green in the colour.</string>
    <string name="greenvaluehelp">This number shows the actual amount of green
        in the colour on a scale from 0 to 255. You can edit the number.
        A single tap on the number will put the edit cursor where you tap;
        a double tap on the number will select the whole of it;
        a long tap on the number will display this message.</string>
    <string name="setbluesliderhelp">Move the thumb on this slider
        to adjust the amount of blue in the colour.</string>
    <string name="bluevaluehelp">This number shows the actual amount of blue
        in the colour on a scale from 0 to 255. You can edit the number.
        A single tap on the number will put the edit cursor where you tap;
        a double tap on the number will select the whole of it;
        a long tap on the number will display this message.</string>
    <string name="sethuesliderhelp">Move the thumb on this slider
        to set the hue. This will not modify the value or saturation,
        which can be set by picking a colour from the map pane.
        Black, white and grayscale colours have a saturation of zero,
        so changing their hue will have no effect.</string>
    <string name="setalphasliderhelp">Move the thumb on this slider
        to adjust the opacity of the widget background:
        zero is transparent and 255 is fully opaque.</string>
    <string name="alphavaluehelp">This number shows the opacity of the background
        on a scale from 0 (transparent) to 255 (opaque). You can edit the number.
        A single tap on the number will put the edit cursor where you tap;
        a double tap on the number will select the whole of it;
        a long tap on the number will display this message.</string>
    <string name="done">Done</string>
    <string name="donehelp">Touch this button or the back button to
        return to the main configuration screen.</string>
    <string name="secondssizerhelp">This slider adjusts the size of the seconds.
        All the way to the left is no seconds at all.
        All the way to the right is the same size as the hours and minutes.</string>
    <string name="nosecondshelp">Touch this end of the slider for a clock
        with no seconds shown.</string>
    <string name="smallsecondshelp">Touch in the middle of the slider for a clock
        with seconds shown at a smaller size.</string>
    <string name="largesecondshelp">Touch this end of the slider for a clock
        with seconds shown at the same size as the hours and minutes.</string>
    <string name="sevensegments">Simulate seven segment LED.</string>
    <string name="sevensegmentshelp">If you really want to waste your high
        resolution display simulating a seven segment LED clock,
        check this box.</string>
    <string name="clockdemo">This half size demonstration shows what
        the full screen clock will look like
        (in %1s orientation at the current ambient light level).</string>
    <string name="landscape">landscape</string>
    <string name="portrait">portrait</string>
    <string name="brightnesshelp">This slider adjusts the minimum brightness
        of the full screen clock at low ambient light level.
        All the way to the left is a minimum brightness of 1 (if your device supports it)
        All the way to the right is no brightness reduction.</string>
    <string name="forcevertical">Force vertical time layout</string>
    <string name="forceverticalhelp">If this box is checked, in portrait orientation
        the hours minutes, seconds if present, and AM/PM marker if present,
        are arranged vertically down the screen. Otherwise if any of
        the numeric date or the full weekday or the full month name
        are displayed, the time is displayed across the screen.</string>
    <string name="setclockcolour">Set full screen clock colour</string>
    <string name="setclockcolourhelp">Touch this button to show a colour
        chooser screen for the colour of the full screen clock.</string>
    <string name="runclock">Test full screen clock</string>
    <string name="runclockhelp">Touch this button to show the full screen clock.
        Touching the screen or the back button from there will bring back
        this screen: this is different from the normal action when the
        clock has been invoked from the top level screen, which is to
        return to the home screen.</string>
</resources>
